A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Latin America and the Caribbean, Jamaica and Mexico City Field Office Files FA612
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1963-1973; IV
  - Law and Development -- "International Legal Studies Programs Supported by the Ford Foundation, 1951 to Date" -- List of Grants, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Population -- Jamaican Marketing Study (Farley and Leavitt), 1968-1972 (Box 7)
  - Population -- St. Vincent Conference (Windward, Leeward and French Islands and Barbados) (69-1), 1968-1970 (Box 7)
  - Sir Arthur Lewis -- Sabbatical Leave in Barbados, 1971, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Committee on Economic Development, 1967-1970 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Agriculture (PA66-210) -- Reports, Basic Documents, Payments, General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Creative Arts Centre (Ref. Humanities and the Arts), 1967-1972 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Department of Government, 1966-1972 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Department of Extra-Mural Studies, 1966-1972 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Faculty of Engineering, 1967-1971 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Faculty of Law, 1967-1970 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Faculty of Medicine, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Faculty of Natural Sciences (incl. report on science and technology education in Venezuela), 1967-1971 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- General (folder 1), 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- General (folder 2), 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- General (folder 3), 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Institute of International Relations, 1966-1970 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Multi-Racial Studies Centre, 1968-1971 (Box 7)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Social Sciences -- Manpower Planning Project -- ISER (L68-68), 1968-1970 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- PA 68-745/Vol.2 -- Management and Education Recruitment, 1967-1970 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- Trinidad, 1967-1972 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies (UWI) -- University Operations Missions (Alexander, Morgan, Stone), 1966-1968 (Box 8)
- Grant and Proposal Files, 1962-1974; V
  - Caribbean -- Association of Caribbean Universities -- UNICA, 1969-1974 (Box 8)
  - Dominican Republic -- Autonomous University of Santo Domingo -- Faculty of Agricultural and Veterinary Sciences (PA65-99), 1967 (Box 8)
  - Dominican Republic -- Texas A&M -- Backstopping Agriculture in the Dominican Republic (PA63-429), 1962 (Box 8)
  - Dominican Republic -- Texas A&M -- Training and Consulting Assistance for SCAD in the DR (64-179), 1963-1969 (Box 8)
  - Education -- UWI Institute of Educatioin (PA62-334), Vol. II -- New Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Local Travel Award (FY1970) -- Gordon, Shirley, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Population -- Ford Foundation Caribbean (L68-103), 1967-1969 (Box 8)
  - Trinidad -- Manpower Advisor to Trinidad Government -- Ajit Das Gupta (PA70-51), 1971 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies -- Demographic Research (PA64-280), 1966-1970 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies -- ISER and Census Program (PA69-589, Vol. 2), 1968-1971 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies -- Reports -- University Centers -- History -- Economics and Management (folder 1), 1966-1972 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies -- University Centers -- Textbook -- History -- Economics and Management (folder 2), 1964-1972 (Box 8)
  - University of the West Indies -- Research in Trinidad in Social Science, 1968-1972 (Box 8)